- This is a very old building.
- Sixty years. Used to be a watch factory.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
(Sheldon:)Don't you worry about the residual radium
from the luminous dials?
(Raj:)Not until now.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe
I didn't bring my Geiger counter.
Yeah, I had it on my bed,
and I didn't pack it.
(Raj:)- If you're not comfortable staying here...
- I'm kidding. I packed it.
It was a joke. Yeah, I was subverting
the conversational expectations.
(Sheldon:)I believe they call that
the old switcheroo.
(Raj:)Terrific.
- Is that woman Aishwarya Rai?
- Yes. Isn't she an amazing actress?
(Sheldon:)Actually, I'd say
she's a poor man's Madhuri Dixit.
How dare you?
(Raj:)Aishwarya Rai is a goddess.
(Raj:)By comparison, Madhuri Dixit
is a leprous prostitute.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, I didn't mean to offend you.